# Henrique Melo

Natal, Rio Grande do Norte, Brazil



henriquework0115@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/henrique-melo-604826248

# **Summary**

Hi, I am Henrique, a Senior WordPress developer with over 14 years of experience. I developed a wide range of WordPress websites. These websites include general sites, business sites, and eCommerce sites with woo-commerce experience. I customize many WordPress themes using builders like Divi and Elementor.

#### Technical Skills:

- Frontend
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Backend
- PHP
- MySQL
- WordPress Codex and APIs
- · Debugging and Troubleshooting
- Ruby on Rails
- Theme Development
- Divi
- Astra
- Avada
- Plugin Development
- Advanced Custom Fields (ACF)
- Toolset Types
- WordPress SEO Plugins
- YoastSEO
- Rank Math
- Form Development
- Contact Form 7
- Gravity Forms
- WPForms
- eCommerce Development
- WooCommerce
- WP eCommerce
- BigCommerce for WordPress

- WordPress Page Builder
- Elementor
- Beaver Builder
- Divi Builder
- Oxygen
- DevOps
- AWS
- Bluehost
- GoDaddy

# **Experience**



# 🥿 Senior Wordpress Developer

Self Employed

2022 - Present (1 year)

#### Senior WordPress Developer

Aktie Now

Feb 2020 - Jun 2022 (2 years 5 months)

# Wordpress Developer

Apr 2017 - Jan 2020 (2 years 10 months)



## Wordpress Developer

Calina Marketing Digital 2014 - 2017 (3 years)



## **Wordpress Developer**

**CMA CGM** 

2011 - 2014 (3 years)



#### **Wordpress Developer**

Sciensa

2008 - 2011 (3 years)

#### **Education**



#### Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte

Bachelor of Computer Science, Computer Engineering 2004 - 2008

#### **Skills**

Blogging • Content Management Systems (CMS) • Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • WordPress Plugin • PSD to Wordpress • PHP • WordPress Theme • Elementor • Theme Development • Wordpress Development